<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-10T11:49:36+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/feed.xml</id><title type="html">KiluaZen</title><subtitle>This a personal blog, an attempt to document my thoughts, ideas and my life as a College Student.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Jan 29</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/29/Jan-29.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jan 29" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/29/Jan-29</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/29/Jan-29.html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s 10:42 PM and I am sad about today so far.</p>

<p>I woke up at 10 AM and was feeling very uneasy, played some guitar, felt fire in my left fingers.</p>

<p>I never played guitar as soon as I wake up before, Then I go to get a hair-cut, which ended up really bad, it was terrible haircut, they were so bad with it, it was awful man. Now I feel so insecure, I used to feel sexy looking myself in the mirror, now I don’t I feel repulsive, I am gonna feel even less confident to talk to women.</p>

<p>Anyway, I don’t know what I will do about that, should I be anxious about how I look, I mean definitely looks matter for the first impressions but after the first conversation it is not that involved anymore.</p>

<p>Funny how, a little haircut can make a mood change so drastically, or I let it do that.</p>

<p>Anyway later I bathed and ate lunch, went to the library and watched graham norton show with Meryll Streep, When I finally decided to write it was last half hour for the library because it was sunday and they close early in the weekends.</p>

<p>Later I wanted to write, I try to figure out locations where I can sit and write, then feel dreadful and decide to go to my hostel. By the meanwhile during walking I have covered all the episodes about Albert Camus in Philosophize This!. I come to the hostel have some snacks even though I wasn’t hungry then watch some more graham norton and go to the gym and it’s 7:45 PM, feel a bit sick like early stages of fever couldn’t do much exercises, so came back feeling bad.</p>

<p>Now on the way back I saw Kriti, obviously didn’t dare to go talk to her now with added insecurity of my hair, I am pretty sure I can carry a conversation but feel terrified to start it, maybe because I run a lot of possible first dialogues in my head before going there. Anyway I will try and talk to her in the future.</p>

<p>Now here I am watched yet another episode of Graham Norton, the one with the Ocean 8’s stars.</p>

<p>I feel regretted about the day then I realise I have a blog website now, it’s a routine to upload the blog’s every sunday. So here we are, and also it’s still 11 PM not too late to fix the day.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s 10:42 PM and I am sad about today so far.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Shadow of DREAD passing over me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/27/A-Shadow-of-Dread-Passing-Over-Me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Shadow of DREAD passing over me" /><published>2023-01-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/27/A-Shadow-of-Dread-Passing-Over-Me</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/27/A-Shadow-of-Dread-Passing-Over-Me.html"><![CDATA[<p>I was walking from the library to my room feeling hungry, thinking of all the things I have done today and for a past couple of days, Today I made a decision not to drop the Machine learning course which I very much feel I am gonna regret, because I think part of the reason I didn’t drop it is I was lazy to go to the admin office, drop deadline was done weeks before.</p>

<p>I tell to myself you are gonna work hard brother, learn machine learning everything works on that in this day and age so it will be useful to learn that, I woke up at 9:15 and watched Mr. Beast podcast and seeing him explain youtube, I went to his youtube channel and watched couple of his videos and saw the things he was talking about like retention and pace of the content, it was 12:30 when I was done with that, later I showered had some lunch, I think I am over consuming food these days, (like I am feeling stomach full which is not a good feeling). Then attended the lab, later I had a class at 5:30 (Flight Mechanics) which I didn’t attend because he asks questions and I don’t have answers because I don’t know the concepts, never given time to learn them, it’s really embarrassing when he asks you can’t say you don’t know, everyone laughs, I feel very anxious going to that class out of very few times I attend. When I went to the library, I started watching youtube some silly youtube videos and then watched good will hunting again.</p>

<p>Later took a nap for 15 min and walking home, felt this shadow of dread all over me.</p>

<p>What am I doing with my life? I have no idea.</p>

<p>I am not passionate about anything, If I am asked what I love to do, I have no answer to give. I just tell aerospace to my parents to escape the conversation with them.</p>

<p>What am I doing missing classes, watching senseless youtube videos for hours.</p>

<p>By the way I feel very connected to Good Will Hunting Movie, I mean I am not that genius, but I am good at math and stuff like that, don’t know what to do with my life.</p>

<p>I like the fact that he is 20 in the movie because I am 20 now too, don’t feel abandoned or anything.</p>

<p>Just you know it’s okay if you read books like writers and lovers or anything they help you in a way, but if you entertain with youtube videos you can’t get back to work in an hour just like that.</p>

<p>Fill you entertainment time with guitar, gym, journaling and stuff like that man, please.</p>

<p>Can you go a week without watching a youtube video. Oh my god I don’t think you can.</p>

<p>show it to me Kushal go without watching a single fucking youtube video for a week.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was walking from the library to my room feeling hungry, thinking of all the things I have done today and for a past couple of days, Today I made a decision not to drop the Machine learning course which I very much feel I am gonna regret, because I think part of the reason I didn’t drop it is I was lazy to go to the admin office, drop deadline was done weeks before.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Realizing my Mistakes</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/25/Realizing-my-mistakes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Realizing my Mistakes" /><published>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/25/Realizing-my-mistakes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/25/Realizing-my-mistakes.html"><![CDATA[<p>Last Night I slept at 2 am, after watching a movie called “Rushmore” by Wes Anderson, it was good, but it made a bit morose, because I am in no clubs at all, none. Well what can I say, I am very much like the idea of it but never got into it, always watched movies and stuff like that and passed time.</p>

<p>Now it’s 11:45 am, I slept for 9 and 1/2 hours, that’s crazy dude, I had a class at 9:30 which I didn’t attend, Kushal you got to put some breaks here what is wrong with you man, you are just being crazy right now. Dude attend the classes, read for the classes, don’t be the old douchebag like your Second year again.</p>

<p>You are not gonna people or talk to them if you sit in your house binging movies and tvshows alright. So enough in three days you have watched 5 movies and two episodes of a tv show(the last of us) it should stop right now, that’s enough.</p>

<p>So by the way yesterday I though watching “Dead Poets Society” again, to get some inspiration, and I watched for half an hour and decided I got to start the poets society again, so I went to Taha’s hostel, proposed the idea he accepted and we went to OAT (open air theatre) , I didn’t want rush into the poems, so we started talking about someone who had a breakup recently and then about my writing classes, later I started reading a book called “five centuries of Engilsh verse” the one they read in the movie, but it was bad it had very old poems. Luckily I had a book with a collection of poems written by Pablo Neruda in my kindle, We read them, they were about love and stuff like that, not really appealing to a bunch of virgins.</p>

<p>I will have to bring a new book with some existential poems next time, “sucking the marrow out of life”.</p>

<p>Anyway the realizations from this blog are, wake up at a specific time, do the class work quickly to have freedom and no regret, stop watching movies, I know they are not bad but there is a line and you have crossed it long ago.</p>

<p>Don’t forget this video, the title feels too much but there are some good points in there.</p>

<p><a href="https://youtu.be/27VugwymWx8">https://youtu.be/27VugwymWx8</a></p>

<p>Remember, not getting distracted is a virtue these days, it wasn’t previously, now we need to constantly fight the algorithms to do our work.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Night I slept at 2 am, after watching a movie called “Rushmore” by Wes Anderson, it was good, but it made a bit morose, because I am in no clubs at all, none. Well what can I say, I am very much like the idea of it but never got into it, always watched movies and stuff like that and passed time.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/21/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2023-01-21T11:33:31+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-21T11:33:31+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/21/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/21/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<p>You’ll find this post in your <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_posts</code> directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">jekyll serve</code>, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</p>

<p>Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:</p>

<p><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP</code></p>

<p>Where <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR</code> is a four-digit number, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MONTH</code> and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">DAY</code> are both two-digit numbers, and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MARKUP</code> is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.</p>

<p>Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Tom'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Check out the <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home">Jekyll docs</a> for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at <a href="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll’s GitHub repo</a>. If you have questions, you can ask them on <a href="https://talk.jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll Talk</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekend Jan 20-22</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/21/Weekend-20-22.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekend Jan 20-22" /><published>2023-01-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/21/Weekend-20-22</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2023/01/21/Weekend-20-22.html"><![CDATA[<p>I had a lot of ambitions this weekend, wanted get a lot of things done, but the end summary was, Watched glass onion, seven psychopaths and the fault in our stars. Also I watched a many actor roundtables, writer roundtables, and director roundtables to a point where I was totally inspired to write a screenplay and direct a movie right now. But when I hear people say it took three years to write the script so, I am like okay it takes time so don’t beat yourself up if you can’t write anything when you just took out pen and a book.</p>

<p>I tinkered a little bit on my jekyll website, I didn’t code much the template was already there I just had upload the blog pages, it was very easy, but there were issues in deploying the website, I couldn’t find where I can change the branch, that is shown on the site, well when I get stuck in a wall like that usually I wait and contemplate on it for 15 min then just hit ctrl+T and type youtube and started watching youtube videos.</p>

<p>I should really cut back on youtube watch, I am going crazy with it, which is bad. I am gonna loose my semester routine if I do that.</p>

<p>I haven’t read anything for my HS class which makes me so sick, don’t know why. The exams are gonna start to kick in pretty quick now.</p>

<p>Also my father called when I was in the library, he gave an impression as if IITB students work really hard and he is like you look tired bro, is everything ok kind of thing, I am like no man don’t imagine me as a ideal IITB student I had no managerial positions at all, and I waste a lot of fucking time man, watching movies and doing stupid things.</p>

<p>By the way I started a book called “Writers and Lovers” by Lily King. So this will the book I am gonna read this week.</p>

<p>Also I newly added “Less”, “Jaws”, “The Creative Act a way of being” into my Kindle library, there are a lot of unread books in the library hope to read them all.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a lot of ambitions this weekend, wanted get a lot of things done, but the end summary was, Watched glass onion, seven psychopaths and the fault in our stars. Also I watched a many actor roundtables, writer roundtables, and director roundtables to a point where I was totally inspired to write a screenplay and direct a movie right now. But when I hear people say it took three years to write the script so, I am like okay it takes time so don’t beat yourself up if you can’t write anything when you just took out pen and a book.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Self Portrait</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/17/Self-Portrait.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Self Portrait" /><published>2023-01-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/17/Self-Portrait</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2023/01/17/Self-Portrait.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="the-day-i-am-20">The day I am 20.</h3>

<p>Hello, I am Kushal, an Aerospace Engineering Student.
Between the computer, phone, and guitar, my whole day passes. People say I don’t talk much, but I can talk if we have some time and one-on-one. It’s harder in the first interactions.</p>

<p>I was born in Chikmagaluru(in Karnataka) 20 years ago, and my family moved to Guntur(in AP) when I was 6 years old.</p>

<p>I was good at studying and scoring grades, which continued until my JEE exams, and once I got my laptop and phone for college, everything changed. I started watching many movies, tv shows and reading books.</p>

<p>All these different perspectives I had never thought about just popped up, and I started recognizing and correcting the stupid ways I used to think.</p>

<p>Amongst the books I have read, The Fountainhead and Atlas Shrugged are just so inspiring and mind-blowing that someone could write that. The topics she talked about in those books, like reasoning and selfishness, were some things I was wired to be against, and just learning her viewpoints had so much influence on me.</p>

<p>I watched many movies in the first two years of college, maybe too many.
I like it when movies mess you up a bit when they make you contemplate your current state. Movies like good will hunting, dead poets society, and tv shows like sex education and Normal people are some, that gave me epiphanies that I wish had occurred to me earlier in my life.</p>

<p>I listen to music a lot and thought it would be cooler if I could play some. So I started learning guitar. As I used to watch many movies, everything I did seemed harder because movies make it look so easy. I thought I would be a Rockstar in a month when I started playing guitar. As it got harder, I gave up, but now I have started learning guitar again as I realized it’s not so much the destination as the journey, and the harder it is, the more rewarding, so if you like it, keep doing it.</p>

<p>I took Aerospace Engineering because I wanted to build rockets,
It’s funny because when you start studying rockets, you would think that you would feel your ability to build them will increase, but it’s actually been the opposite. It seems so complicated and not possible now that I know the nitty-gritty of things. It may seem daunting, but I still want to pursue my goal.</p>

<p>The best things I do in my day are brushing my teeth at night while standing in front of a mirror, thinking about what I have done that day and what I want to do tomorrow. The other best thing is walking to classes while listening to podcasts.</p>

<p>I have been listening to Lex Fridman and Joe Rogan podcasts a lot. They are great.
In Podcasts, you get to be in a conversation with people you admire, Podcasts are long, and they leave you with content.</p>

<p>I got into an argument with my mother once. She was telling me to prepare for the placements. I got exasperated, partly because I couldn’t explain to her the way I was thinking about it, that placements are too short-term of a goal and blah blah blah, then I felt guilty that I got angry at her, from her perspective it totally made sense, by the way, my mother and I have a minimal relationship, we rarely open up, and when she did I got angry, and I felt so guilty about that, that’s when I decided,</p>

<p>I want to be stoic in my arguments and serene in my actions.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day I am 20.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nov 28</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/28/Nov-28.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nov 28" /><published>2022-11-28T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/28/Nov-28</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/28/Nov-28.html"><![CDATA[<p>I booked a cab to Dadar Railway Station. So he left me after ceossing through a huge bridge just beside platform 7.</p>

<p>Where is my train indicated that the train would be at pf 7. So I thought I am here and stayed there quiet a while.</p>

<p>I had a dejavu that I don’t recall this to be like this from my previous encounters.</p>

<p>Later I went to the swarch of people.</p>

<p>And with help of google found that. There is two parts of Dadar. Dadar Central and Dadar Western. And I was in dadar western pf7 , whilst I had to be at Dadar Central.</p>

<p>Finally I went there and there my train was .</p>

<p>Also about today.</p>

<p>Fucking ear pain is back again.🙌also I went to get a hair cut but there was no one there .And Me and Hrishikesh are working out together.</p>

<p>We do Abs together. Its soo goood.</p>

<p>I feel my stomach muscles dude.</p>

<p>We done it twice, I hope we continue after coming back tooo.</p>

<p>Anyway I will do the 10 min ab workout even when I am home.</p>

<p>I hope I will be as productive as I ever been and more.</p>

<p>I completed Midnight Libraries, made me cry a little. When she comes back to her life and his brother comes to see her. It was great dialogue there, I ennacted it and cried such a great experience.</p>

<p>Also I wil hug my mother when I am home, I never done that before, no idea why. If you don’t express no one will ever know.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I booked a cab to Dadar Railway Station. So he left me after ceossing through a huge bridge just beside platform 7.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Day</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2022/11/21/my-day.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Day" /><published>2022-11-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2022/11/21/my-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/jekyll/update/2022/11/21/my-day.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello People, Today I am working on building this website and launching it via github free hosting services.
I wanted a blog website for over six months, I learnt traditional web development, learnt React, node, mogoose for this and then.<br /></p>

<p>Here I am building a website using jekyll.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello People, Today I am working on building this website and launching it via github free hosting services. I wanted a blog website for over six months, I learnt traditional web development, learnt React, node, mogoose for this and then.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nov 20</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/20/Nov-20.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nov 20" /><published>2022-11-20T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/20/Nov-20</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/20/Nov-20.html"><![CDATA[<p>Well well well…… I had my Aerodynamics Exam today AE333 which was really great, the exam that I was most prepared of, so what can I say, I actually didn’t have time to answer all the questions, I always used to have time to contemplate on questions because there weren’t much that I could answer, but here I felt like I could answer all the questions.</p>

<p>Then Later I came back and started reading the Midnight Libraries, and slept reading it for a while.</p>

<p>I don’t know after the reviewer gave a slightly less review for this book, the enthusiasm flew away a little bit, I shouldn’t really totally depend on his review, I got to have my own opinions.</p>

<p>Well it’s a great book I am gonna read it and see for myself how it is..</p>

<p>This weird feeling that I am gonna post a status of this book as soon as I finish it, I hate that whenever it creeps in, just read it if you like it and you can think about posting it later.</p>

<p>Also I went to the gym early today and I was talking to Taha while I was there on my phone and roaming around and I saw a girl (blue died hair), sitting there alone and playing with carrom coins, so I went up there and said “ Are you waiting for someone or can I join “, she immediately said yes and directed me the chair, and I introduced myself her name was Verniti ( I think I am not sure already in just 4 hours).</p>

<p>Well we played a best of three and she won, but talked a lot, about her PHD in game theory and also about Taylor Swift and about various other things.</p>

<p>I guess we strongly connected on the Taylor swift things and I didn’t stutter anywhere in my talk( mostly English a little bit of Hindi too) she was from UP(near Lucknow).</p>

<p>Over all I think she was also a easy person to talk tooo and the conversation had a background of carroms so, It made the pauses seem ok.</p>

<p>Well this is great I should do this often.</p>

<p>My first female stranger talk in IITB ain’t that something.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well well well…… I had my Aerodynamics Exam today AE333 which was really great, the exam that I was most prepared of, so what can I say, I actually didn’t have time to answer all the questions, I always used to have time to contemplate on questions because there weren’t much that I could answer, but here I felt like I could answer all the questions.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nov 06</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/06/Nov-06.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nov 06" /><published>2022-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/06/Nov-06</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testing/2022/11/06/Nov-06.html"><![CDATA[<p>Well I am writing this on 7 Nov, So what did I do yesterday aaaah I can’t remember , well I have quizzes to prepare on 7,8 nov bet I didn’t do that.</p>

<p>I tried to read Rocket Propulsion and AE651 stuff but I guess miserably failed at it, Well I ended up watching few movies and practiced guitar</p>

<p>I am playing chords with the help of guitar tuna app, I can take practice tests where it keeps displaying chords for some time and gives rank at the end its fun kind of like how I am obsessed on taking typing tests again and again.</p>

<p>About Movies, I watched a movie called ‘We are your friends’ it’s about a DJ so I decided to learn DJing it would be a pretty good party skill to have.</p>

<p>Web3 development professional, guitar personal, DJ party look it’s clear now and don’t forget Aerospace Hobby.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Web3 development professional, guitar personal, DJ party ,look it’s clear now and don’t forget Aerospace Hobby.</p>

</blockquote>

<p>and also a movie called ‘Unpregnant’ its a comedy it was good too just showing how people can be.</p>

<p>I may have spent a lot of time browsing for movies, I know I know man what kind of a person I am becoming right …. well what can I say dude it is what it is…</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>It is never what it is . It is what it should be and what it could be. - - - Ayn Rand</p>

</blockquote>

<p>So what could I be and what do I want to be. I want to be get pleasure by reading and learning things like the other day when I was learning about nozzles and I saw a video Elon explaining his engines and I got to understand some of it, that felt really rewarding.</p>

<p>I guess my movie learning has reached its threshold and at this point I am just wasting time, being in a numb state with nothing to think just sitting there and letting the time go by.</p>

<p>Ok enough with that;</p>

<p>I made a layout for my blog website yesterday its in my diary.</p>

<p>Gotta learn React quickly and start working on it.</p>

<p>I hope I have a fully functional blog by the end of this year. I talked to a guy he said It should be that difficult if you know the stuff.</p>

<p>I also want to mention this I feel like I am missing all the things I can learn from my Aerospace branch by skipping classes and not preparing for exams, I kind of feel bad about that.</p>

<p>Also yesterday my father called and we talked about the money I have and he said he would send me 10k, man I feel bad and relieved , relieved because I was feeling ashamed to ask for money and bad because I don’t have a source of income of my own.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well I am writing this on 7 Nov, So what did I do yesterday aaaah I can’t remember , well I have quizzes to prepare on 7,8 nov bet I didn’t do that.]]></summary></entry></feed>